themogulmom.com 2011-12-29

# Policies | The Mogul Mom

The Mogul Mom takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our website and/or register for daily emails from The Mogul Mom. Please read this notice carefully.

**Personal Information**

In order to supply you with The Mogul Mom daily email, we need your email address. The Mogul Mom does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. The Mogul Mom will never sell, rent, or share your personal information, including your email address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. The Mogul Mom may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering email to you or as required by law.

**Non-Personal Information**

The Mogul Mom may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data. Though this information is optional, we may use it to improve our site and/or tailor your experience on our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising in The Mogul Mom daily email or on the site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information**

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, The Mogul Mom may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers’ use of The Mogul Mom daily emails and the website. This information is not personally identifiable and will be used only to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on The Mogul Mom site, from which sites subscribers came, and to what sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver The Mogul Mom daily email.

**Review and Access**

Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update, or modify this information.

**Choice/Opt Out**

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no future notices.

**Third-Party Advertising**

Some of the ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you by our Web advertising partner or partners. Information about your visit to their site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about our advertising partners, cookies, and how to opt out, please contact us.

**Tracking**

Like most sites, The Mogul Mom makes use of browser cookies. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. The Mogul Mom will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services. The Mogul Mom also uses transparent GIF images. We use these images to track the emails that we send out.

**Third-Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Links to Other Sites**

As part of the service, The Mogul Mom may create links allowing you to access third-party sites. The Mogul Mom is not responsible for the content that appears on these sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult the sites’ individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security**

All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Modification to This Policy**

The Mogul Mom may change this policy, but we’ll post any changes here, so be sure to check in from time to time.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us.

Last Updated: 12/21/2011
